<resources>
    <string name="app_name">assignment2</string>

    <string name="exercise1">   1. Stand upright with your legs together, arms at your sides. \n\n
                                2. Bend your knees slightly, and jump into the air.\n\n
                                3. As you jump, spread your legs to be about shoulder-width apart. Stretch your arms out and over your head.\n\n
                                4. Jump back to starting position.\n\n
                                5. Repeat.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise2">   1. Lie down with you operated knee straight.\n\n
                                2. Bend your non-operated knee as shown. \n\n
                                3. Tighten your core muscles and your thigh muscle and slowly raise your operated leg to the level of your opposite knee. \n\n
                                4. Your leg should remain straight. \n\n
                                5. Then slowly lower the leg.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise3">   1. Kneel on the floor.\n\n
                                2. Extend arms and put hands shoulder-width apart on the floor in front of you.\n\n
                                3. Tighten abs while you bend arms, lowering your torso until chest grazes the floor.\n\n
                                4. Push torso back up by straightening arms. Slow and steady.\n\n
                                5. Rinse and repeat.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise4">   1. Lie face down on a mat with your arms stretched above your head. (like Superman)\n\n
                                2. Raise your right arm and left leg about 5 to 6 inches off the ground (or as far as you comfortably can).\n\n
                                3. Hold for 3 seconds and relax.\n\n
                                4. Repeat with the opposite arm and leg.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise5">   1. Lie on your back, legs bent and together.\n\n
                                2. Keep your legs bend and lift them all the way up to the ceiling until your butt comes off the floor.\n\n
                                3. Slowly lower your legs back down till they’re just above the floor. Hold for a moment.\n\n
                                4. Raise your legs back up. Repeat.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise6">   1. Start with your body in a straight line and your hands slightly wider than shoulder-width apart. Keep your toes and balls of the feet touching the floor.\n\n
                                2. Bring one knee up toward the center of your stomach and then quickly alternate between legs.\n\n
                                3. Continue alternating until the set is complete.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise7">   1. Lie on an exercise mat, with your back flat, knees bent and your feet flat on the floor slightly wider than shoulder-width apart.\n\n
                                2. Fully extend your arms down the side of your body, palms facing in. This is the start position.\n\n
                                3. Exhaling, crunch your torso forward and to the right until you can touch your right heel with your right hand. Hold for a count of one.\n\n
                                4. Return to the starting position smooth motion, inhaling as you do so.\n\n
                                5. Repeat the movement, this time to your left side.\n\n
                                6. When you have completed the movement on both sides, you have done one repetition.\n\n
                                7. Repeat.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise8">   1. Assume a push-up position but bend your arms at your elbows so your weight rests on your forearms.\n\n
                                2. Tighten your abs, clench your glutes and keep your body straight from head to heels.\n\n
                                3. Hold as long as you can.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise9">   1. Lie on your right side with your legs straight and feet stacked on top of each other. Place your right elbow under your right shoulder with your forearm pointing away from you and your hand balled into a fist. The pinky side of your hand should be in contact with the ground.\n\n
                                2. With your neck neutral, breathe out and brace your core.\n\n
                                3. Lift your hips off the mat so that you’re supporting your weight on your elbow and the side of your right foot. Your body should be in a straight line from your ankles to your head.\n\n
                                4. Hold this position for the duration of the exercise. Depending on your fitness level, aim for between 15 to 60 seconds.\n\n
                                5. Repeat on your left side.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise10">  1. Stand with your feet hip-width apart, keep your back straight, your shoulders back, and your abs tight.\n\n
                                2. Take a step forward and slowly bend both knees, until your back knee is just above the floor.\n\n
                                3. Stand back up and repeat the movement.\n\n
                                4. Alternate legs until the set is complete.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise11">  1. Start with your feet wider than your hips and your knees and toes pointing forward.\n\n
                                2. Shift your weight into your right heel, push your hips back, and bend that knee while leaving your left leg straight.\n\n
                                3. Then, drive through your right foot to reverse the movement.\n\n
                                4. Repeat on the other side.
    </string>
    <string name="exercise12">  1. Keep your head straight and your neck and jaw muscles relaxed.\n\n
                                2. Relax your shoulders and keep them back and down.\n\n
                                3. Bend your arms at a 90° angle and keep your hands relaxed (but not floppy).\n\n
                                4. Lean forward slightly, without bending at the waist.\n\n
                                5. Square your hips and keep them stable.
    </string>

    <string-array name="title_story">

        <item>Build Lean Muscle</item>
        <item>Lose Fat</item>
        <item>Improve Metabolism</item>
        <item>Vegan Diet</item>
        <item>Low calorie</item>
        <item>Control BMI</item>
        <item>Good Eating Habits</item>
        <item>Having A Good Night Sleep</item>

    </string-array>

    <string-array name="details">

        <item>  -Eat Lots of nuts\n
                The very first must-do for the skinny guy/gal is to start snacking on nuts regularly.
                Nuts are easy to pack and carry around with you and can easily provide a good 300+ calories per handful.\n\n

                -Eat dried fruits\n
                Another quick trick to help get more calories in is to also opt for dried fruit rather than fresh
                fruit more often. While fresh fruit is definitely healthy and part of a good muscle-building diet, \n
                it will fill you up more quickly than dried fruit will.\n\n

                -Eat oats cold\n
                Oatmeal is a fantastic carbohydrate source that’s recommended in any diet for gaining
                muscle, but for skinny athletes, they will want to serve this one up cold. Cooked oatmeal
                takes up far too much room in the stomach and will instantly cause you to feel full, on very
                few calories.\n\n

                -Eat plenty of lean meat and fatty fish\n
                lean red meat and fatty varieties of fish are going to be excellent for the skinny guy and gal
                because they not only provide the protein you need to build more lean muscle mass, but they’re
                also going to give you some healthy fat as well. This means you’ll take in more calories overall
                with these choices, moving you closer to your goal to experience safe muscle gain.\n\n
                While chicken and turkey can also definitely be eaten, make sure to consume
                higher-calorie protein sources at least a few times per week.\n\n

                -Drink your calories\n
                The next quick tip for the skinny athlete is to make sure you drink some of your calories.
                Chocolate or regular milk, protein smoothies for extra nutrients are all terrific options for you.\n\n
        </item>



        <item>
                -Eat plenty of soluble fiber\n
                Soluble fiber absorbs water and forms a gel that helps slow down food as it passes through
                your digestive system.\n\n

                -Avoid foods that contain trans fats\n
                Trans fats are created by pumping hydrogen into unsaturated fats, such as soybean oil.\n\n

                -Don’t drink too much alcohol\n
                Oatmeal is a fantastic carbohydrate source that’s recommended in any diet for gaining
                muscle, but for skinny athletes, they will want to serve this one up cold. Cooked oatmeal
                takes up far too much room in the stomach and will instantly cause you to feel full, on very
                few calories.\n\n

                -Eat plenty of lean meat and fatty fish\n
                lean red meat and fatty varieties of fish are going to be excellent for the skinny guy and gal
                because they not only provide the protein you need to build more lean muscle mass, but they’re
                also going to give you some healthy fat as well. This means you’ll take in more calories overall
                with these choices, moving you closer to your goal to experience safe muscle gain.\n\n
                While chicken and turkey can also definitely be eaten, make sure to consume
                higher-calorie protein sources at least a few times per week.\n\n

                -Drink your calories\n
                The next quick tip for the skinny athlete is to make sure you drink some of your calories.
                Chocolate or regular milk, protein smoothies for extra nutrients are all terrific options for you.\n\n
        </item>



        <item>
                -Eat Plenty of Protein at Every Meal\n
                Eating food can increase your metabolism for a few hours.
                This is called the thermic effect of food (TEF). It’s caused by the extra calories required to digest,
                absorb and process the nutrients in your meal.\n\n

                -Drink More Cold Water\n
                People who drink water instead of sugary drinks are more successful at losing weight and keeping it off\n
                Studies have shown that drinking 17 ounces (0.5 liters) of water increases resting metabolism
                by 10–30% for about an hour\n\n

                -Lift Heavy Things\n
                Muscle is more metabolically active than fat, and building muscle can help increase your metabolism\n
                This means you will burn more calories each day, even at rest\n\n
        </item>

        <item>
            -Carbohydrates\n
            Athletes aren’t the only ones who need carbohydrates. A vegan diet is rich in this macronutrient,
            which means fiber, antioxidant, and phytochemical intake is strong, too.Example food:\n
            Rice\n
            white pasta\n
            white bread\n\n\n
            Other important foods include:\n
            Protein: legumes, grains, tofu, quinoa, nuts, seeds, vegetables\n
            Omega 3 fatty acids: flax seeds, chia seeds, hemp seeds, walnuts, seaweed\n
            Vitamin B12: nutritional yeast\n
            Iron: legumes, grains, nuts, seeds, green vegetables\n
            Zinc: beans, nuts, seeds, oats, nutritional yeast\n
            Calcium: kale, broccoli, bok choi, beans, almonds, sesame seeds,
            fortified plant-based milk and juices\n
            Iodine: seaweed, potatoes, white beans, cranberries, iodized salt\n
        </item>

        <item>
            -Berries\n
            Berries — including strawberries, blueberries, raspberries and blackberries — are loaded with vitamins, minerals and antioxidants that can optimize your health.
            Their high fiber content also boosts weight loss and reduces hunger.\n
            For example, 1 cup (148 grams) of  blueberries supplies just 84 calories but packs 3.6 grams of fiber\n\n

            -Eggs\n
            Eggs are extremely nutrient-dense, as they’re low in calories but rich in many vital nutrients.\n
            A single large egg has approximately 72 calories, 6 grams of protein and a wide array of important
            vitamins and minerals.\n
            In a study in 30 women, those who ate eggs for breakfast instead of a bagel experienced
            greater feelings of fullness and consumed 105 fewer calories later in the day\n
            Studies suggest that starting your day with a serving of eggs can reduce hunger and boost fullness.\n\n

            -Legumes\n
            Because of their high protein and fiber content, legumes such as beans, peas and lentils can be incredibly filling.\n
            One cup (198 grams) of cooked lentils provides about 230 calories, as well as 15.6 grams of
            fiber and nearly 18 grams of protein.\n
            Multiple studies prove that legumes have a powerful effect on hunger and appetite.\n
            One study in 43 young men noted that a high-protein meal with beans and peas increased feelings of fullness
            and reduced appetite and hunger more than a high-protein meal with veal and pork
            Another review of nine studies reported that people felt 31% more full after eating pulses,
            a type of legume, compared to high-carb meals of pasta and bread\n\n

            -Popcorn\n
            Thanks to its high fiber content, popcorn tops the charts as one of the most filling low-calorie snacks.\n
            Though there are only 31 calories in 1 cup (8 grams) of air-popped popcorn, it boasts 1.2 grams of dietary fiber —
            up to 5% of your daily fiber needs \n
            Not only does fiber slow your digestive process to promote fullness, but it can also
            stabilize blood sugar to prevent hunger and cravings .\n\n



        </item>

        <item>
            -Track Your Weight Loss Progress Closely\n
            Know where you stand today — and where you stood yesterday. Then give yourself a pat on the back.
            “Self-monitoring is really important when it comes to weight control,” says O’Neil.\n\n
            He recommends recording your food or calorie intake for a few days to understand what
            your eating habits are truly like. “Many patients will come back and say, ‘I never knew how much I ate,’”
            he explains.\n\n
            It may be the reality check you need to change your habits. Use whatever method you feel most comfortable
            with, whether that’s writing it in a journal or using an app on your smartphone. A February 2019
            study published in Obesity found that the more frequently participants used a web app to track
            their diet habits over six months, the more weight they lost.\n\n\n\n

            -Stay Consistent, Even if You Aren’t Seeing Results Right Away\n
            Even if the weight doesn’t seem like it’s coming off fast enough, stay the course.
            It’s only with consistent efforts to eat well, move more, and maintain other healthy
            habits that affect weight (like getting enough sleep) that the pounds come off permanently,
            research suggests. Researchers found that when weight jumped up and down — possibly because
            of inconsistent efforts — people were more likely to give up on their goals. Remember: You’ve got this.\n\n\n\n



        </item>

        <item>
                -Listen to your body.\n
                You may not feel full right away, but that doesn’t mean that you
                should keep eating until you feel uncomfortable.\n\n
                Eat when you feel hungry, not when you’re bored. Mindless eating when you’re not even
                hungry leads to an excessive calorie intake of less nutritious foods.\n\n
                Eat slowly. Focus on the tastes and textures of your food. Enjoy your food rather
                than inhaling it! Be sure to slow down so that you can feel the hunger go away and feel a comfortable,
                full feeling take over.\n\n
                Learn to be mindful while eating. Mindful eating will teach you how to eat
                when you’re hungry and stop when you’re satisfied. You’ll also learn to genuinely
                taste your food and enjoy the tastes of healthier foods.\n\n\n\n


                -Don’t skip meals\n
                Skipping meals slows your metabolism and might even make you gain weight.
                It also causes your blood sugar levels to drop.\n\n
                Always eat breakfast. Eating a healthy breakfast at a reasonable hour is great for your metabolism
                and keeps your hunger in check throughout the day.\n\n
                Keep healthy snacks available at work. Hunger pains at work make it easy to grab a
                bag of greasy chips from the vending machine. Always stay prepared for hunger at work
                by keeping nuts, rice cakes, veggie chips or other healthy snacks at your desk. Check out
                this awesome article by Nutrition Advance for 99 healthy snack ideas!\n\n\n\n

                -Always pay attention to the labels\n
                Learn to decode nutrition labels. Always check sugar, sodium, saturated fat, and trans fat amounts.\n\n
                Check the ingredient label. Learn sneaky terms for hidden sugar and other additives. If a
                food product contains too many ingredients that you can’t pronounce, put it back on the shelf!\n\n\n\n
</item>

        <item>
                Foods that help you sleep well\n\n\n\n
                -Almonds
                It’s been claimed that almonds may help boost sleep quality as well. \n\n
                This is because almonds, along with several other types of nuts, are a source of the hormone melatonin.
                Melatonin regulates your internal clock and signals your body to prepare for sleep\n\n\n\n



                -Turkey
                It’s high in proteinThe protein in turkey may also contribute to its
                ability to promote tiredness. There’s evidence that consuming moderate amounts of
                protein before bed is associated with better sleep quality, including less waking up throughout the night\n\n\n\n

                -Kiwi
                Kiwis are a low-calorie and very nutritious fruit\n\n
                In a 4-week study, 24 adults consumed two kiwifruits one hour before going
                to bed each night. At the end of the study, participants fell asleep 42% more quickly
                than when they didn’t eat anything before bedtime.\n\n\n\n

                Several other foods and drinks have sleep-promoting properties. For example, they may contain
                high amounts of nutrients such as tryptophan.\n\n
                However, in some cases, there’s little research into their specific effects on sleep.\n\n
                Dairy products: Dairy products, such as a glass of milk, cottage cheese, and plain yogurt,
                are known sources of tryptophan. Milk has been shown to improve sleep in older adults,
                especially when paired with light exercise \n\n
                Bananas: Banana peels contain tryptophan and the fruit itself is a modest source of magnesium.
                Both of these properties may help you get a good night’s sleep \n\n
                Oatmeal: Similar to rice, oatmeal is high in carbs with a bit more fiber and has been reported to
                induce drowsiness when consumed before bed. Additionally, oats are a known source of melatonin\n\n

        </item>

    </string-array>


</resources>